It feeds on the darkness within.
The Assent is a horror, thriller film directed by Pearry Reginald Teo.
After a series of disturbing supernatural events in his home, Joel a young
single father, comes to suspect that his young son may be possessed.
Soon Joel receives a visit from Father Lambert, a controversial exorcist
in town whose last patient died during his treatment.
As increasing chilling occurrences begin to unfold, the priest informs a resistant Joel that unless he
can successfully perform an exorcism, the devil will soon take full control of his boy.
Joel, played by Robert Kazinsky.
Father Lambert, played by Peter Jason.
Cassie, played by Hannah Ward.
Dr. Hawkins, played by Tatum O'Neal.
Mason, played by Caden Dragomer.
Brother Michael, played by Douglas Spain.
Royal assent is the method by which a monarch formally approves an act of the
legislature, either directly or through an official acting on the monarch's behalf.
In some jurisdictions, royal assent is equivalent to
promulgation, while in others that is a separate step.
Under a modern constitutional monarchy, royal assent is
considered little more than a formality.
Even in nations such as the United Kingdom, Norway, the Netherlands, Liechtenstein and Monaco which still, in theory, permit their monarch to
withhold assent to laws, the monarch almost never does so, except in a dire political emergency or on advice of government.
While the power to veto by withholding royal assent was once exercised often by European
monarchs, such an occurrence has been very rare since the eighteenth century.
Royal assent is typically associated with elaborate ceremony.
In the United Kingdom the Sovereign may appear personally in the House of Lords or may appoint Lords Commissioners, who
announce that royal assent has been granted at a ceremony held at the Palace of Westminster for this purpose.
Royal assent is usually granted less ceremonially by letters patent.
In other nations, such as Australia, the governor-general (as the Monarch's
representative) has the right to dissolve the parliament and to sign a bill.
In Canada, the governor general may give assent either in person at a ceremony in the Senate or
by a written declaration notifying Parliament of their agreement to the bill.
The tone is dark and intense.